One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Fight, crash through, and face the challenge!
These are our hard knock days.
Can't quench our thirst with a peaceful, everyday life.
Here we go - don't ever run away!
Let's go on living as the mighty winds take us!
We've still got so far to go.
Gotta keep going through the hard knock days.
Let's do it again, yes, baby. How many times
do I have to stand back up to make my dream come true?
Feels like the strength of my resolve
is put to the test everyday.
Hey, let's go!
I don't want to make excuses and settle for being mediocre.
We leapt into a crazy, lawless world.
As I struggled for a foothold, reality caught me off guard.
Even if it beats me, hits me, knocks me down again,
Oh!
Only when we get back on our feet and look forward,
will we have the last laugh, be the winners!
We gotta go down this glory road, till we reach our goal!
Fight, shake it off, act strong!
These are our hard knock days.
There's no such thing as a safe choice.
Here we go - we'll always be the strongest!
Let's keep moving - never mind the consequences.
Let's put our wishes all together,
and keep on going through the hard knock days.
Gear Fourth
Run! Run!
Run to the center of the island!
Th-The buildings that haven't been sliced apart yet...
...are being pushed by the cage and closing in on us!
The country's growing smaller and smaller!
Royal Palace Grounds - Second Level
The bird cage is shrinking?
So that's what's causing all the commotion.
This is the true terror of the bird cage, dear!
I can't believe this!
This is a really big deal!
Oh! I called him "dear" again!
I can't just stand here and wait for death
while sucking my thumb!
Rouse our fallen allies right away!
Alright!
Former
Royal Plateau
If the battle lasts long enough,
this plateau will be cut into pieces, too.
What?! I thought this was the center of the country!
Isn't this the safest place?
Look at the sky!
The center of the bird cage is shifting, little by little.
The center of contraction is probably the current Royal Palace Grounds, where Doflamingo is!
Royal Palace Current Location
That means this place will eventually...
Hurry up, Hack! Please hurry up!
Stop shaking me!
We have finally descended,
but there seems to be quite the commotion!
That way, huh?
Zoro-dono!
Where are you going?
It's obvious, isn't it?
I'm going to stop it, of course!
That!
"That"?
Outside the Palace
Sunflower Field
What a surprise.
I didn't know there were dwarfs in Dressrosa.
I hope your arm is reconnected properly.
They said when blood starts flowing, it's cured.
I know. I'm a doctor.
When I saw the underground trade port, I understood.
This battle...
Even if we do take down Doflamingo, it won't be over.
It'll cause tremendous ripples across the world.
And you guys will be the eye of the storm.
Yeah.
That's the plan.
"Gear Fourth"?
That's right.
Muscle Balloon!
Gear...
Fourth!
Bound-Man!
Whoa, whoa, is this some kind of joke?
You've grown quite large.
I thought you had an ace
up your sleeve or something...
You can't even stand up straight,
being all rubber and bouncing like that.
How're you gonna send me flying like that?
For two years,
I fought against monstrously huge, savage beasts!
To force them into submission,
I needed this giant body and bounciness!
How will bounciness help you...
Shut up!
You won't...
be able to do a damn thing!
Rubber...
Kong...
Gun!
I-It's Doflamingo!
But why?
Back off, back off!
Why are you here, Doflamingo?!
That's what I'd like to know!
Run! He's gonna kill us all!
There's nowhere to run!
It's just the bird cage out there!
Downtown, eh?
I was flung pretty far...
He's bouncing off the air!
Rubber...
Rhino Schneider!
Somebody else came!
He's huge! And he kicked Doflamingo away!
Who is that ball-like guy?
Dammit!
By hardening his skin with the Color of Arms,
he's multiplied its tension!
That ball bastard!
He's nothing but rubber!
I told you!
You're no match for Gear Fourth!
Rubber...
Culverin!
Athlete String!
He's hardened, yet still rubbery?!
Attacks like that...
won't work!
I can't believe this!
You won't get away, Mingo!
I'm gonna kick your ass!
Why?! Now he just keeps stretching!
Keep going after him, Python!
Enough! Down you go!
Rubber...
Culverin!
That rubber ball is...
...overwhelming...
...Doflamingo!
Who is that guy?!
Who cares who he is?!
Go for it!
You can do it!
Royal Palace Grounds
Did you see that?!
Yeah...
I can't believe how he changed.
Is that really Straw Hat?
He's overpowering the formidable Doflamingo!
He's amazingly strong!
But he's overusing his Haki.
Overusing his... Haki?
Oh, there he is.
They went to play somewhere else.
And here I took the trouble to come and watch them!
Captain of the first ship of the
Blackbeard Pirates, Jesus Burgess.
Why is he here?
Chase 'em or wait for 'em...
Either way, I won't let 'em get away!
I'm gonna get what I came for!
Just as I thought, he's after Luffy-kun and the others.
But what's he really after?
Corrida Colosseum
Viola.
So, all that remains is the decisive battle between him and Luffy-kun?
Yes, that's right, Father.
Of those ranked commander and above,
Doflamingo is the only one remaining!
SMILE Factory
Outta the factory, Tontattas!
Okay!
We're outta here!
Get a super move on and get out!
We've finished rescuing our stranded friends in the factory!
Alright!
The factory is tilting!
Fraland! Why is the Smile Factory the only building that isn't being cut up?
"Only" the factory?
I get it, it's the Sea Stone!
Sea Stone?
Yeah, the outer walls of the factory are made of Sea Stone.
So strings created by a Devil Fruit user can't cut it...
But, look!
It's starting to be pushed!
Hm? That's...
Franky!
Oh, Robot-dono!
Zoroland! Topknotland!
Hey, Zoro, Kin'emon!
The center of the country is in the direction you just flew from.
If you wanna run, you're going the wrong way!
We ain't running!
We're gonna stop the strings!
Stop them?
Oh, I didn't even think about that!
What?! That's so cool!
Until Luffy settles this, we gotta buy some time!
Oh yeah!
Downtown
Luffy vs. Doflamingo
Using the Color of Arms to control the expansion and contraction of his rubber body any way he wants...
A harmony of Arming and Rubber, huh?
If I take too much time, Gear Fourth's gonna...
You seem like you have excellent grasp of your abilities, but it must be quite the burden.
Surely there are some risks.
Rubber...
Straw Hat, how many more
seconds will you last?
...Double...
My strings, however, will never run out!
...Culverin!
Off-White String!
H-How are his strings
coming out of the ground?!
What did you do to this town?!
Listen up, fledgling!
Devil Fruit abilities have yet another stage to them, called "Awakening"!
The buildings turned into strings!
In rare instances, an ability will "awaken"
and begin to affect things other than its user's body!
All kinds of things are turning into strings!
This doesn't look like the power of a Paramecia!
Anything that surrounds you, I can turn to string!
You can't even come near me!
And when your strength gives out,
my body will have...
The moment your Haki gives out, I'll finish you off!
20 Minutes
Later
It's gonna slice us! Run!
Oh, Grandma!
Grandma, stand up! The strings'll cut you!
I can't...
I can't run anymore...
Leave me here and go on ahead.
No way, no way! I can't do something like that!
I won't survive this anyway.
Please, get up!
Even if I get up,
I definitely can't run all the way downtown!
Somebody, give us a hand!
There are still patients in the hospital!
We can't carry them all by ourselves! I'm begging you!
My son's missing! Has anyone seen him?!
He's wearing a Kuma shirt! He's five years old!
Anybody! Have you seen my son?!
We're all gonna die anyway.
We should just give up.
No matter how far we run, we're still in a cage.
We'll all be killed by Doflamingo.
It's easier...
if we just give up.
Everybody, please listen to me.
This is...
the former king of Dressrosa, Riku Dold the Third.
Wh-What?
K-King Riku...
Currently, our country is trapped within an inescapable bird cage,
as part of a game started by the current king, Doflamingo.
In addition, that vicious bird cage continues to shrink, carving up the town with it.
King Riku...
All too suddenly, reality befell all of you.
I am sure your emotions have not had the chance to catch up to you,
and right now you are simply trying to save your own life, or the life of someone else!
However, this is not a dream!
Nor is this a tragedy that has begun only today!
For a decade,
we have lived in this bird cage called "Dressrosa",
under the reign of pirates!
For a decade, we lived as puppets manipulated by them.
Such is our reality!
However, that shall soon end!
The Donquixote Family that we thought nobody could match...
...is on the verge of defeat, at the hands of the mighty warriors
that are in this country by coincidence!
The Family's commanders have already fallen!
Really?!
Those commanders were...
He's saying they were taken down?
The only enemy remaining to be defeated...
is the current king of Dressrosa, Doflamingo!
And the one fighting him is the pirate, Straw Hat Luffy!
I believe that he is the man
that will destroy this bird cage!
Whether he wins or loses,
it will be over in less than an hour!
Until then, survive! Do whatever it takes!
I do not want a single one of you to be crushed by this shrinking country!
Please, keep running!
Even if you run out of breath, or if your legs break!
Stay alive for just a few more minutes!
There is still hope!
Please don't give up!
We'll give it our all, even without help!
Okay!
Alright! Let's get goin', grandkid!
'Kay, Grandma!
Me, too!
Just like King Riku said...
We won't give up! We're running downtown!
Carry the sick!
Grab those beds!
Mommy!
Survive until the battle ends!
Straw Hat Luffy's gonna take down Doflamingo for us!
Uh-huh!
Mingo!
About time you dropped dead.
I'm runnin' out of time!
The whole town's turning to string!
Billow White!
Mingo!
I'm gonna blow you away!
I'm ending this!
Rubber...
Leo Bazooka!
D-Do...
Doflamingo!